healthtoday.me 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Company Practices Regarding Your Privacy**

We at healthtoday.me are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web site. 

healthtoday.me has established the following Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of healthtoday.me. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that healthtoday.me does not own or control. 

**Personally Identifiable Consumer Information**

We do not collect any personally identifiable information. If you place an order with one of our partners they will collect and retain your information. Please review their privacy policy for how your information will be handled. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information**

healthtoday.me collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the healthtoday.me site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site. healthtoday.me may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information. 

**How Collected Information is Used**

The non-personally identifiable information that healthtoday.me collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We do not share the non-personally identifiable information that healthtoday.me collects. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out**

Our web site utilizes cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting healthtoday.me. 

**Your Consent**

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. 

**Contacting Us**

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding healthtoday.me's Privacy Policy, you may contact us.
